# **Erikas Taroza**

#### **PROFILE**

I am an experienced software developer with a diverse set of skills including Flutter/Dart, web development, Git, and Linux. My journey in software development is marked by my drive to constantly grow my skills and my commitment to excellence. I am also an active contributor to the open-source community. I maintain my own projects as well as help fix various bugs in other open-source projects.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

January 2023 - March 2024

## Full Stack Developer, IDMSRTV (Startup)

- Implemented core functionality of product
- Drove strategy for website development
- Identified and implemented modern technologies to get the beta website to market faster
- Collaborated with cross functional team leaders to define project scope and timelines
- Rewrote WordPress website with improved styling and functionality
- · Frameworks/languages used
  - Angular
  - Vue
  - Java (Android app)
  - Rust
  - o PHP
  - WordPress

# October 2022 - December 2022 Intern Web Developer, Deidis (Startup)

- Developed widget to provide clients an easy way to capture leads
- · Frameworks/languages used
  - React
  - NodeJS

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### **Google Cloud Certified**

Google Cloud Associate Cloud Engineer (2023)

See Certificate

#### **PROJECTS**

October 2022 - Present

#### simple\_audio

- A simple cross-platform solution for playing audio in Flutter
- Rust
- · Open source

May 2022 - Present

#### **BitBeat**

- Music streaming app with no ads
- Docker
- Frameworks/languages used
  - Flutter
  - Vue
  - Rust

**December 2020 - Present** 

## **Open Source**

Contributing to open source projects by fixing issues, adding new features, or creating my own open source projects.

See my work here: <a href="https://github.com/erikas-taroza">https://github.com/erikas-taroza</a>

June 2016 - July 2020

# **Multiplayer Game Development**

- 2D platformer
- Unity 5 Unity 2019
- Unreal Engine 4

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Cloud	Frontend	Backend	Languages
<ul><li>GCP</li><li>AWS</li><li>Vultr</li></ul>	<ul><li>Flutter</li><li>Vue</li></ul>	<ul><li>Express.js</li><li>MySQL</li><li>SurrealDB</li><li>Axum</li><li>Parse Server</li></ul>	<ul> <li>Dart</li> <li>JavaScript</li> <li>TypeScript</li> <li>Rust</li> <li>C#</li> <li>Java</li> <li>Python</li> </ul>

### **EDUCATION**

July 2019 - January 2023 Laurel Springs School

High School

- 3.75 GPA (3.90 weighted)
- AP Computer Science (4/5 on AP exam)

July 2016 - Present Self-Taught

I taught myself everything I know about programming.